Finding aid for Mike Wallace CBS/60 Minutes Papers, 1922-2007
Bentley Historical Library
- General Files
  - 1989
    - * Personal
      - Press Coverage (Box 92)
      - Resumes (Box 92)
      - 60 Minutes Press Coverage (Box 92)
      - Speeches/Appearances
        - Marketing Conference of the Systems Integration Division, IBM, April 14 (Marco Island, FL) (Box 92)
        - Center for Communication, April 27 (New York, NY) (Box 92)
        - University of Pennsylvania Commencement, May 22 (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 92)
        - Pitney, Hardin, Kipp & Szuch (law firm), May 24 (Springfield, NJ) (Box 92)
        - Fidelity Investments, September 14 (Boston, MA) (Box 92)
        - David Wolper Tribute, Museum of Broadcasting, September 15 (New York, NY) (Box 92)
        - John Hancock Financial Services, November 3 (New York, NY) (Box 92)
        - United States Tennis Association National Junior Tennis League Brunch, December 3 (New York, NY) (Box 92)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 92)
      - Wallace Fiction Prize, Yale University (Box 92)
    - Topical
      - Ideas-Cape Town, South Africa (Box 92)
      - Ideas-Michael Milken (Box 92)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Newsnotes and Comment, CBS News, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - 60 Minutes Bluesheets (brief story topics), 1988-1989; 3 folders (Box 92)
      - Taking Part If You Drop Out, Don't Drive, September 20 (Box 92)
      - Salute to Mike Wallace, September 23, 1989 (Box 92)
  - 1990
    - Administrative Various, 8 folders (Box 134)
      (include bluesheets)
    - * Speeches/Awards/Appearance, 22 folders (Box 134)
    - Correspondence A-Z, 7 folders (Box 135)
    - Assistant's Correspondence, A-H only (Box 135)
    - Telephone Registers (Box 135)
    - Invitations, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - * UM Activities/Events, 4 folders (Box 136)
    - * Personal Various, 5 folders (Box 136)
    - Topical, 1990
      - Auction Prizes-CBS Tours, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - News Notes/ Radio, 1990 (Box 136)
      - Tom Braden (Box 136)
      - Rooney (Andy) (Box 136)
      - Ben Hecht Project (Box 136)
      - Eye on New York (Box 136)
  - 1991
    - Administrative Various, 6 folders (Box 136)
    - * Speeches/Appearances/Awards, 1991; 3 folders (Box 136)
    - * Speeches and Awards, 15 folders (Box 137)
    - Correspondence A-Z, 5 folders (Box 137)
    - Memos to and from MW, 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Assistant's correspondence (Box 137)
    - * Personal Various
      - Telephone register (Box 138)
      - Invitations (Box 138)
      - Financial (Box 138)
      - Accounting memos (Box 138)
    - Topical, 1991
      - Violence in America (Box 138)
      - Whose Side Are You On? (Box 138)
  - 1992
    - Administrative Various, 7 folders (Box 138)
    - * Speeches/Appearance/Awards, 2 folders (Box 138)
    - * Speeches/Appearance/Awards, 13 folders (Box 139)
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 139)
    - * Personal Various
      - Telephone register (Box 139)
      - Assistant's correspondence (Box 139)
      - Invitations (Box 140)
      - Memos to and from MW, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Topical, 1992
      - Age in America (Box 140)
      - Archetype Associates: Frank Lloyd Wright (Box 140)
      - Artists (Box 140)
      - Watergate Transcripts (Box 140)
  - 1993
    - Administrative Various, 6 folders (Box 140)
    - * Speeches/ Appearance/Awards, 17 folders (Box 140)
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 141)
    - * Personal various
      - Assistant's correspondence (Box 141)
      - Invitations (Box 141)
      - Memos to and from MW, 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Topical
      - Auction Prizes (Box 141)
      - Sheldon Hackney (Box 141)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright (Box 141)
  - 1994
    - Administrative Various, 3 folders (Box 141)
    - Administrative Various, 4 folders (Box 142)
    - * Speeches/ Awards/ Appearances Various, 8 folders (Box 142)
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 142)
    - Assistant's correspondence (Box 142)
    - Topical
      - Germany (Box 142)
      - Hezbollah (Box 142)
      - Lighthouse (Box 142)
      - O.J. Simpson (Box 142)
      - Tyson Clips (Box 142)
      - UM (Box 142)
      - Michigan Weekend (Box 142)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright (Box 142)
      - 20th Century, 3 folders (Box 142)
      - JFK/ Warren Commission (Box 143)
      - Manson Family (Box 143)
      - Cuba/ Bay of Pigs (Box 143)
      - Camelot/ Chappaquiddick (Box 143)
      - Apollo/ Challenger (Box 143)
  - 1995
    - Administrative Various, 3 folders (Box 143)
    - * Speeches/ Appearances/ Awards Various, 5 folders (Box 143)
    - * Goldsmith Award, Harvard University, March 9, 1995 (Box 143)
    - Correspondence Various, 4 folders (Box 143)
    - Telephone Registers (Box 144)
  - 1996
    - Administrative Various, 5 folders (Box 144)
    - * Speeches/ Appearances/ Awards, 17 folders (Box 144)
    - Correspondence Various, 4 folders (Box 145)
  - 1997
    - Administrative Various, 2 folders (Box 145)
    - * Speeches/ Appearances/ Awards Various, 9 folders (Box 145)
    - Correspondence Various, 4 folders (Box 145)
  - 1998
    - * Speeches/ Appearances/ Awards Various, 9 folders (Box 146)
    - Correspondence Various, 6 folders (Box 146)
    - Topical, 1998
      - Martin Luther King Jr. Papers (Box 146)
      - 20th Century (Box 146)
  - 1999
    - *Speeches/ Appearances/ Awards Arab-American Anti-Discrimination Coalition (Box 146)
- * Personal/Biographical
  The Personal/Biographical series consists of files set apart by Wallace and his staff. Although composed mainly of articles and clipping either written by, or about, Mike Wallace, this series also includes files pertaining to collections of Mike Wallace papers and visual materials at other repositories and a set of "reporters' notepads" used by Wallace as part of interviews or when he reported from the field.
  - Mike Wallace materials at other archives
    - Syracuse University (1958-1962) (Box 93)
    - UCLA Film and Television Archive (1958-1959) (Box 93)
    - University of Texas (1957-1958)
      - General (Box 93)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright Materials (Box 93)
  - Biographies, 1957-1981 (Box 93)
  - Scrapbook of clippings and articles, 1968-1974 (Volume 1)
  - Clippings and Articles Regarding Mike Wallace
    - 1942-1958 (Box 93)
    - 1964-1970 (Box 93)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 93)
    - 1977 (Box 93)
    - 1978 (Box 93)
    - 1979 (Box 93)
    - 1980
      - General (Box 93)
      - Parade Article and Press Coverage (Box 93)
    - 1981 (Box 93)
    - 1982
      - General (Box 93)
      - San Diego Bank and Racial Slur Press Coverage (Box 93)
    - 1984-1989 (Box 93)
    - 1991-2012 (Box 93)
  - Reporters' Notebooks, 1966-1970; undated; 29 volumes (Box 93)
  - Speeches, Unidentified (Box 93)
  - Biographies and clippings about MW, 1990s (Box 147)
  - Biographies and clippings about MW, 1990s (Box 148)
    (continued)
  - Biographical miscellanea (from MW home) (Box 149)
    (includes clippings, photos, scripts from early television programs, etc.)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series includes photographs, U-matic, VHS, and Betacam videotapes.
  - Photographs
    Personal photographs are mostly formal and informal portraits of Wallace and members of his family, dating from 1922, as well as photographs taken during award ceremonies and various public events. A large portion of professional photographs relates to 60 Minutes segments and other broadcasts between 1967 and 1993. The photographs illumine the behind-the-scenes of 60 Minute segments and of Wallace's interaction with political and social notables: presidents, entertainment and sports figures, and headline makers in general. Among photographs are images from the 1968 Richard Nixon campaign, Robert F. Kennedy, Israeli military leader and politician Moshe Dayan, Palestinian leader Yasser Arafat, Iraqi President Saddam Hussein, leader of the Communist Party of China Deng Xiaoping, Canadian Prime Minister Pierre Trudeau, Attorney General John Mitchell, the Black Panther party leader Eldridge Cleaver, composers Leonard Bernstein and Aaron Copeland, pianist Vladimir Horowitz, actress Bette Davis, entertainer Johnny Carson, boxer Mohammad Ali, among others.
    - Personal
      - Portraits (Box 94)
        - 1922-1984 (Box 94)
          (see also outsize folder UAm)
      - To, 1977
        - Brookline, Massachusetts and Early Photos (includes slide), 1926-1939 (Box 94)
        - Navy, 1945-1946 (Box 94)
        - Award Ceremony, 1957 (Box 94)
        - Golden Shoe Awards, Shoe and Allied Industries Division of the United Jewish Appeal (includes Saul Schiff and New York Yankee Gil McDougald), June 20, 1957 (Box 94)
        - Honorary Chairmanship, New Jersey Asthma Crusade, April 1959 (Box 94)
        - Wallace Family, 1962-1982 (Box 94)
        - Mike Wallace, Arlene Francis, and Gary Moore Judging for the Bedside Network, November 1963 (Box 94)
        - American Women in Radio and Television Lunch, January 23, 1968 (Box 94)
        - Columbia-DuPont Awards, January 30, 1973 (Box 94)
        - "More" Convention, 1974 (Box 94)
        - Dinah Shore Show, 1975 (Box 94)
        - Bill Buckley Roast (Mike Wallace and Nancy Kissinger), Summer 1977 (Box 94)
      - 1978-1985
        - United Counties Trust Company, May 3, 1978 (Box 94)
        - National Association of Purchasing Management, May 17, 1978 (Box 94)
        - Honorary Degree, University of Massachusetts, May 27, 1978 (Box 94)
        - Robert Saudek (Museum of Broadcasting), 1980 (Box 94)
        - White House, 1981 (Box 94)
        - I Love a Clean New York Publicity Photograph, 1982 (Box 94)
        - Amway Corporation Event and "Larry King Live" Appearance (Grand Rapids, MI) (includes Amway President Rich DeVos, Larry King, Beach Boy Al Jardine, Amway Chairman of the Board Jay Van Andel, and Betty Ford), October 12, 1983 (Box 94)
        - CBS Twenty and Thirty Year Awards (see outsize folder UAm), 1983 (Box 94)
        - Promenade Lecture Series, New College/University of South Florida (Sarasota), April 14, 1985 (Box 94)
      - 1987-1989
        - Photograph of Mike Wallace with Pat and Al Haig, 1987 (Box 94)
        - Mike Wallace Fellowship in Investigative Reporting, University of Michigan, April 18, 1989 (Box 94)
        - Center for Communication Award Luncheon (includes Ed Nay, Katharine Graham, Mary Wallace, and Mike Wallace) (New York, NY), April 27, 1989 (Box 94)
        - First Pitch at Wrigley Field, Chicago, IL, October 1989 (Box 94)
        - "A Salute to Mike Wallace," Museum of Broadcast Communications, Chicago, IL, September 23, 1989 (Box 94)
      - 1990-1993
        - Emmy Hall of Fame (with Angie Dickenson), January 7, 1990 (Box 94)
        - CBS News Correspondents on Donahue, May 17, 1990 (Box 94)
        - Iran, 1990 (Box 94)
        - People's Choice Awards with Don Hewitt (60 Minutes Producer), March 14, 1991 (Box 94)
        - Award Ceremony with James Garner, 1991 (Box 94)
        - Richard Nixon (with Melanie, Jennie, and Alex Eisenhower and Christopher Cox), 1993 (Box 94)
      - Undated
        - Baseball, undated (Box 94)
        - Barbara Bush, undated (Box 94)
        - CBS (formerly framed), undated (Box 94)
        - Pauline Friedman Lederer (Ann Landers), undated (Box 94)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 94)
        - Moscow, undated (Box 94)
        - Passport Photographs and Business Cards, undated (Box 94)
        - Portraits, undated; 3 folders (Box 94)
        - Tennis (includes slides and negatives), undated (Box 94)
    - Professional (largely related to 60 Minutes segments and other broadcasts)
      - circa 1951-1968
        - Mike and Buff, (see also outsize folder UAm), circa 1951-1953 (Box 94)
        - Adventure, CBS-TV, July 1953 (Box 94)
        - The Big Surprise Errol Flynn, February 12, 1957 (Box 94)
        - Samuel D. Hawking (Prisoner of War in China), June 24, 1957 (Box 94)
        - Philip Wylie, 1957 (Box 94)
        - Nightbeat ABC, (includes Diana Barrymore, Cleveland Amory, Mickey Cohen, Earl Browder, Henry Cabot Lodge, and Mary Margaret McBride), 1957-1959 (Box 94)
        - "Close-Up U.S.A.", 1960 (Box 94)
        - Oleg Penkovsky (Soviet official charged with espionage), May 11, 1963 (Box 94)
        - Saturn Rocket Launch (with Lyndon B. Johnson), January 29, 1964 (Box 94)
        - Political Conventions, 1964 (Box 94)
        - The Beatles, circa 1964-1969 (Box 94)
        - "The National Citizenship Test,", November 9, 1965 (Box 94)
        - "Classroom U.S.A." (Vietnam), December 7, 1967 (Box 94)
        - Richard Nixon Campaign, 1968 (Box 94)
        - Political Conventions (see also outsize folder UAm), 1968 (Box 94)
        - Inauguration, 1968 (Box 94)
        - 60 Minutes, Formal, 1968-, circa 1980 (Box 94)
        - 60 Minutes General, 1968- (see also outsize folder UAm), circa 1980 (Box 94)
      - 1969-1972
        - Darryl Zanuck, March 28, 1969 (Box 94)
        - H.L. Hunt, 1969 (Box 94)
        - Captain Ernest Medina (My Lai incident), 1969 (Box 94)
        - Northern Ire, 1969 (Box 94)
        - "Eldridge Cleaver and the Black Panther Party,", January 6, 1970 (Box 94)
        - "Aaron Copeland at 70,", November 24, 1970 (Box 94)
        - "Interview with Walter Hickel" (Secretary of the Interior), November 24, 1970 (Box 94)
        - "Interview with Canadian Prime Minister Pierre Trudeau,", December 8, 1970 (Box 94)
        - Mohammad Ali (includes slide), 1970 (Box 94)
        - Attorney General John Mitchell, 1970 (Box 94)
        - Vietnam (includes slides), 1970 (Box 94)
        - William Crum, "How to Succeed in the PX Business Without Really Trying" (military retail post exchange system), March 16, 1971 (Box 94)
        - "Moshe Dayan" (Israeli Defense Minister), April 13, 1971 (Box 94)
        - Cooper, D.B. (1971 Northwest skyjacking mystery; includes photos) (Box 94)
        - "Clifford Irving" (Howard Hughes biography), January 16, 1972 (Box 94)
      - 1973-1979
        - Farah Pahlavi, 1973 (Box 94)
        - "Egil Krogh" (White House 'plumber': break in to The Pentagon Papers' Daniel Ellsberg's psychiatrist's office), January 27, 1974 (Box 94)
        - "Oil and the Shah of Iran,", March 10, 1974 (Box 94)
        - CBS News (includes Connie Chung), 1974 (Box 94)
        - Carroll O'Connor, 1974 (Box 94)
        - Washington Post Staff (includes Benjamin Bradlee, Katharine Graham, and Bob Woodward), 1974-, circa 1990 (Box 94)
        - G. Gordon Liddy, "The Man Who Wouldn't Talk...Talks,", January 5, 1975 (Box 94)
        - "[H.R]. Haldeman: The Nixon Years,", March 1975 (Box 94)
        - Syrian Jews, 1975 (Box 94)
        - "Vladimir Horowitz" (pianist), December 26, 1977 (Box 94)
        - Johnny Carson, "Here's...Johnny,", April 29, 1979 (Box 94)
        - "[Yasser] Arafat,", March 18, 1979 (Box 94)
        - Ted Armstrong, circa 1979 (Box 94)
      - 1980-1985
        - "Bette Davis,", January 20, 1980 (Box 94)
        - Leonard Bernstein, "Lenny,", February 10, 1980 (Box 94)
        - Ronald and Nancy Reagan, July 1980-January 1989 (Box 94)
        - Jerry Falwell and Lowell Weicker, "Morality and the New Right," Up to the Minute, October 3, 1981 (Box 94)
        - 60 Minutes Assistants, 1981 (Box 94)
        - "Up to the Minute" with Mike Wallace (includes slides), 1981 (Box 94)
        - China, 1981-1986 (Box 94)
        - Joseph Bonanno, "Man of Honor," (reputed leader of organized crime), March 27, 1983 (Box 94)
        - "Helen Hayes" (actress), December 4, 1983 (Box 94)
        - General William Westmoreland Libel Suit, 1984-1985 (Box 94)
        - "Donahue" (profile of Phil Donahue), February 24, 1985 (Box 94)
        - AP Trial, April 1985 (Box 94)
        - "Who Is Bob Harris?" (multiple sclerosis sufferer, influential in Senator Jesse Helms' Fairness in Media campaign), September 15, 1985 (Box 94)
      - 1986-1993
        - "Deng Xiaoping" (from interview in Beijing), September 7, 1986 (Box 94)
        - "Sam Hall" (American arrested for spying in Nicaragua), December 21, 1986 (Box 94)
        - Nicaragua, 1987 (Box 94)
        - Election Night, 1988 (Box 94)
        - Admiral William Crowe, (Chairman, Joint Chiefs of Staff) "Voyage of Discovery,", September 17, 1989 (Box 94)
        - "Felix Rodriguez" (interview with former CIA member, involved in many agency operations in Latin America and Vietnam since 1960), October 22, 1989 (Box 94)
        - Rock Newman, February 1993 (Box 94)
      - Undated
        - "Close Encounters" Cover Photograph, undated (Box 94)
        - Noel Coward, undated (Box 94)
        - Morton Downey, Sr. and Lee Ann Weimer, WGN Radio, undated (Box 94)
        - Barry Goldwater, undated (Box 94)
        - Robert F. Kennedy, undated (Box 94)
        - Barry Londo Visa Application Photographs, undated (Box 94)
        - Military Interviews, undated (Box 94)
        - Miscellaneous interview photographs (Box 94)
        - George Schweitzer, CBS News, undated (Box 94)
      - Prints of scanned images (Box 94)
        (originals framed and on walls of MW's office)
  - Videotapes
    - Videotapes (U-matic)
      - "The Hate That Hate Produced" (Black Muslims), July 23, 1959; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - Election Night coverage (Mike Wallace appearances)Visual, 1986; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - 60 Minutes segment featuring floor of the House of Representatives and Representative Livingston, 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - 20/20 program featuring Barbara Walters and Mike Wallace, 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - "Taking Part" (20 minutes), October 25, 1989; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - 60 Minutes segment Brown v. Koch, January 24 and June 12, 1988; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - Ed Murrow Excerpts, 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
      - Jeffrey Wigand Case
        - Tobacco, January 26, 1996; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
        - Tobacco, January 29, 1996; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
        - CBS News -- 60 Minutes, November 12, 1995; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
        - CBS News Broadcasts, January 29, January 31, and February 1, 1996; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
        - 60 Minutes (Off-Air Recording), February 4, 1996; 1 videotape (U-matic) (Box 95)
    - Videotapes (VHS)
      - Bottom Line proposed interview program produced by Jan Helfeld, 1992; 6 videotapes (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - ASAE Boston Convention featuring speech by Donald Trump, 1989; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - Saddam: Interview with Saddam Hussein (Jews of Baghdad, aftermath of Gulf War, 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - 60 Minutes interview with Edward Teller, November 13, 1988; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - Television Academy Hall of Fame Show, November 20, 1993; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - "All about TV" (Richard Salant Tribute), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - The 20th Century with Mike Wallace
        - "America's Other Assassins" (1995), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - National Press Club-Don Hewitt Lunch, October 17, 1995; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - "Earthquakes: Living on the Edge" (1995), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - "First Ladies" (1994), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - "Persian Gulf War" (1995), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - "Uprising at Attica" (1995), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - Dead Blue: Surviving Depression (HBO) regarding Wallace's battle with depression, 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - The 60 Minutes Deception: An Expose of Media Corruption, 1997 Citizens for Honest Government (Regarding Vincent Foster's 1997 death), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - Jeffrey Wigand Case
        - 60 Minutes Broadcasts
          - "Blowing Smoke,", March 24, 1996; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
          - "Jeffrey Wigand, Ph.D.,", February 4, 1996; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
          - "Up in Smoke,", March 24, 1994; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - CBS Evening News Broadcasts
          - Regarding Jeffrey Wigand Case, November 29, 1995; January 26, 1996; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
          - Regarding Jeffrey Wigand Case, 1996 January 31; 1996 January 27; February 1, 1996; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - Charlie Rose Broadcasts (Box 96)
          - " 60 Minutes" (regarding CBS management decision not to run tobacco piece), September 13, 1995; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
          - Interview with 60 Minutes Staff on success of show (also mentions tobacco tapes deposition), May 6, 1997; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - CNN Broadcasts
          - Brown and Williamson's charge against CBS for the Sixty Minutes Tapes, February 15, 1996; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
        - WHAS Broadcast
          - Jeffrey Wigand's History through Court Records, January 18, 1996; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 96)
      - Louis Farrakhan, April 1, 2000; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Committee of 100 Headliner Journalism Award, April 26, 2001; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
        (MW role in ceremony)
      - "Insidious Killer: Chemical and Biological Weapons" (20th Century with Mike Wallace), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - "A Passion for Justice" (Richard LaPointe Case), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Closeup U.S.A. (Arkansas Black Family), August 1960; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - The Mike Wallace Interviews. With William O. Douglas, May 18, 1958; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - MW being interviewed by foreign correspondents on topic of assisted suicide and Dr. Jack Kevorkian, May 23, 2002; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - "The Mock Trial of Doctor K. (United Ann Ter Films), 2000; 2002; 2 copies, 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
        (include MW views of assisted suicide and Dr. Jack Kevorkian)
      - 60 minutes segment: KIPP (Knowledge in Power Program), September 1999; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - 60 minutes segment: Oprah (Oprah Winfrey), December 14, 1986; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Mike Wallace Interview program: Interview with Charles (?) Kelly (World War II Congressional Medal of Honor winner), 1950s; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Oldenburg, 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
        (includes early interview with this artist)
      - CBS News (WCBS Channel 2) segment re Mike Wallace and his CD "The Girl She's Mine", February 8, 2001; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Mike Wallace on Charlie Rose program, June 17, 2002; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - The Race for Space (David L. Wolper production), 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - 60 Minutes-25th Anniversary Special, November 14, 1993; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Magnus interview MW on case of tobacco and Brown and Williamson on the CBS Eve. News, November 10, 1995; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
      - Television in America: An Autobiography with Mike Wallace, October 28, 2002; 1 videotape (VHS (TM)) (Box 154)
    - Videotapes (Betacam; 20 minute tapes) (Box 97)
      - 60 Minutes segment "Melinda", 1990; 2 videotapes (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - TV 50, 1989; 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - CBS Evening News Segment on Jeffrey Wi, November 29, 1995; January 26, 1996; 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - Soros Foundation, 2 videotapes (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
    - Videotapes (Betacam; 30 and 60 minute tapes)
      - Ramstein Air Base, Germany, 1982; 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - Soros Foundation, 1989; 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - Adm. William J. Crowe Jr. interview or, 1988; 1989; 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - Sandy Goodman's tapes (various segments), 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
      - Arafat interviews, 1977; 1979; 1989; 1 videotape (Betacam (TM)) (Box 97)
- Sound recordings
  - Reel-to-reel